

An individual who spend 22 years of his life in IT for banking and financial services, public sector, and manufacture, with passionate to create, deliver and drive technology as values to customer to achieve their goals. George helped to define and demonstrate the important role to provides industry insight/technology trends, correlate with technology capability and apply architectural thinking & methodologies in translating customer business requirements into solutions.

Currently, he focuses on software defined networking technology, infrastructure security, and cloud to help customer transforming their infrastructure into cloud.

## **Key Skills**

- + Strategic Planning
- + Consultative Selling
- + End-to-end Enterprise Network Architect
- + Infrastructure Security
- + Cloud Technology
- + Operating Systems (Unix, Linux, and Windows)

# George Bratadidjaja

Https://www.linkedin.com/in/gbratadidjaja

Tech Architect Manager – Accenture Technology

Email: gbratadidjaja@gmail.com | Mobile: +62817800718

**Accenture Indonesia** 

### Education

Jun 2018 - Now

+ Computer Science, September 1996, Gunadarma University, Depok - Indonesia

## **Professional Experience**

	Accenture Technology – Tech Architecture Manager
Jan 2017 – Jun 2018	Independent Consultant Technical Architect
Apr 2006 – Dec 2016	<b>Cisco Systems Indonesia</b> System Engineer for Public Sector, Banking, and Manufacture
Jan 2004 – Mar 2006	PT Anabatic Technologies Senior Network Engineer for Banking and Financial Services
Jul 1999 – Dec 2003	PT Nusantara Compnet Integrator Network Engineer for Public Sector (Ministry of Finance)

### **Certifications**

- + AWS Practitioner (active)
- + Cisco Certified Network Professional (R&S)
- + Cisco Certified Design Professional (R&S)
- + Cisco Firewall

### **Honors and Awards**

- + System Engineer Excellence Award FY14
- + System Engineer Sales Champion FY12

### Courses

- + Accenture Architecture Assessment School
- + CISSP Bootcamp
- + TOGAF 9.1
- + Design Thinking
- + Story Telling
- + Consultative Selling
- + Presentation Skill
- + Cisco Transition and Leadership Program
- + Various of Technical, Sales, and Leadership Readiness Training

### **Past Projects**

Jun 2018 - Now

#### **Accenture Indonesia**

#### Australia, Indonesia - Network Transformation Services and Network Transformation Project

- The project focused on architecting network and security (readiness for zero trust architecture), include implementation of network segmentation, network analyzer, next generation firewall, and network redundancy. Role: Network Architect and Delivery Lead
- Indonesia IT Management Assessment
- The project focused on assessing IT operating model, application, Infrastructure, and security in communication service provider company. Role: Network and Security Infrastructure Team Lead

#### Indonesia – IT Transformation Project

• The project focused on transforming IT infrastructure including cloud, network, security in a managed service company. Responsible to create standardization of products, configuration, security, technical documentation, and delivery plan. Role: Technical Lead.

### Indonesia - Network Architect and Support Services

 The project focused on architecting network in managed service company. Responsible for creating high level design and low-level design, migration scenario, and technical documentation. Role: Team Lead

### Indonesia – LAN Operation Services

• The project focused in managing and monitoring network to meet customer SLA. Role: Team Lead.